Toggle navigation [Home](https://www.privatoria.net/ "Privatoria")

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how  
we collect, use, communicate and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

When accessing the https://www.privatoria.net website, will learn certain  
information about you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilizes a standard technology called ‘cookies’ (see explanation  
below) and server logs to collect information about how our site is used. Information gathered through cookies and  
server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our site, and the websites  
visited just before and just after our own, as well as your IP address.

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a  
website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive  
specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s  
preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has  
already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

### IP Addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that  
is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web  
server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you  
request) can be sent to you.

### Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with  
your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we  
employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone. This also applies when you register  
for our website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address or make a purchase on this site. For  
further information see the email policies below.

### How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing  
customer service and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our  
site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise  
transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the  
law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

### Email Policies

We are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential. We do not sell, rent, or lease our subscription lists  
to third parties, and we will not provide your personal information to any third party individual, government  
agency, or company at any time unless strictly compelled to do so by law.

We will use your e-mail address solely to provide timely information about .

We will maintain the information you send via e-mail in accordance with applicable federal law.

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mail sent from our organization will clearly state who the e-mail is from  
and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also contain  
concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further e-mail  
communication from us.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners by reading  
the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of any e-mail they receive from us at anytime.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these  
communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail.

### Use of External Links

https://www.privatoria.net may contain links to many other websites. cannot  
guarantee the accuracy of information found at any linked site. Links to or from external sites not owned or  
controlled by do not constitute an endorsement  
by or any of its employees of the sponsors of these sites or the products or  
information presented therein.

By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all  
applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws.  
If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials  
contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.

### Intellectual Property Rights

All copyrights, trademarks, patents and other intellectual property rights in and on our website and all content and  
software located on the site shall remain the sole property of or its licensors.  
The use of our trademarks, content and intellectual property is forbidden without the express written consent  
from .

**You must not:**

* Republish material from our website without prior written consent.
* Sell or rent material from our website.
* Reproduce, duplicate, create derivative, copy or otherwise exploit material on our website for any purpose.
* Redistribute any content from our website, including onto another website.

### Acceptable Use

You agree to use our website only for lawful purposes, and in a way that does not infringe the rights of, restrict or  
inhibit anyone else’s use and enjoyment of the website. Prohibited behavior includes harassing or causing distress  
or inconvenience to any other user, transmitting obscene or offensive content or disrupting the normal flow of  
dialogue within our website.

You must not use our website to send unsolicited commercial communications. You must not use the content on our  
website for any marketing related purpose without our express written consent.

### Restricted Access

We may in the future need to restrict access to parts (or all) of our website and reserve full rights to do so. If,  
at any point, we provide you with a username and password for you to access restricted areas of our website, you  
must ensure that both your username and password are kept confidential.

### Use of Testimonials

In accordance to with the FTC guidelines concerning the use of endorsements and testimonials in advertising, please  
be aware of the following:

Testimonials that appear on this site are actually received via text, audio or video submission. They are individual  
experiences, reflecting real life experiences of those who have used our products and/or services in some way. They  
are individual results and results do vary. We do not claim that they are typical results. The testimonials are not  
necessarily representative of all of those who will use our products and/or services.

The testimonials displayed in any form on this site (text, audio, video or other) are reproduced verbatim, except for  
correction of grammatical or typing errors. Some may have been shortened. In other words, not the whole message  
received by the testimonial writer is displayed when it seems too lengthy or not the whole statement seems relevant  
for the general public.

is not responsible for any of the opinions or comments posted  
on https://www.privatoria.net. is not a forum for testimonials, however  
provides testimonials as a means for customers to share their experiences with one another. To protect against  
abuse, all testimonials appear after they have been reviewed by management of . doe not share the opinions, views or commentary of any testimonials  
on https://www.privatoria.net – the opinions are strictly the views of the testimonial source.

The testimonials are never intended to make claims that our products and/or services can be used to diagnose, treat,  
cure, mitigate or prevent any disease. Any such claims, implicit or explicit, in any shape or form, have not been  
clinically tested or evaluated.

### How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private  
information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may  
enter on our website may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit  
Card information and other sensitive information is never transmitted via email.

may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such  
purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and  
least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem  
areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all  
users, uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized  
attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

### Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability

makes no representations, warranties, or assurances as to the accuracy, currency or  
completeness of the content contain on this website or any sites linked to this site.

All the materials on this site are provided ‘as is’ without any express or implied warranty of any kind, including  
warranties of merchantability, noninfringement of intellectual property or fitness for any particular purpose. In no  
event shall or its agents or associates be liable for any damages whatsoever  
(including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, business interruption, loss of information, injury or  
death) arising out of the use of or inability to use the materials, even if has  
been advised of the possibility of such loss or damages.

### Policy Changes

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that  
if the privacy policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under  
this privacy policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this privacy policy, without your prior  
consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the  
confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

### Contact

If you have any questions regarding this policy, or your dealings with our website, please contact us  
here:

[  
**$4.92/month with this link**  
](https://go.nordvpn.net/aff_c?offer_id=15&aff_id=1158&url_id=1476&source=privatoria)

* * *

[  
**Only $3.33/month with this link**  
](https://www.privatoria.net/goto-purevpn)

* * *

[  
**Only $2.25/month with this link**  
](https://www.privatoria.net/goto-cyberghost)

**2018 PRIVATORIA.NET**
